<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Valorant Companion App</string>

    <!-- LoginActivity / Register Activity -->
    <string name="login_welcome">Welcome!</string>
    <string name="login_email">Email</string>
    <string name="login_password">Password</string>
    <string name="reg_register">Register!</string>
    <string name="reg_riotid">RiotId: (e.g. ValorantUser123)</string>
    <string name="reg_tagline">Tagline: (e.g. #1234)</string>

    <string-array name="ranks">
        <item>Rank</item>
        <item>Unranked</item>
        <item>Iron 1</item>
        <item>Iron 2</item>
        <item>Iron 3</item>
        <item>Bronze 1</item>
        <item>Bronze 2</item>
        <item>Bronze 3</item>
        <item>Silver 1</item>
        <item>Silver 2</item>
        <item>Silver 3</item>
        <item>Gold 1</item>
        <item>Gold 2</item>
        <item>Gold 3</item>
        <item>Platinum 1</item>
        <item>Platinum 2</item>
        <item>Platinum 3</item>
        <item>Diamond 1</item>
        <item>Diamond 2</item>
        <item>Diamond 3</item>
        <item>Immortal</item>
        <item>Radiant</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="regions">
        <item>Region</item>
        <item>SEA</item>
        <item>EMEA</item>
        <item>NA</item>
        <item>OCEANIA</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="agents">
        <item>Agent</item>
        <item>Brimstone</item>
        <item>Phoenix</item>
        <item>Sage</item>
        <item>Sova</item>
        <item>Viper</item>
        <item>Cypher</item>
        <item>Reyna</item>
        <item>Killjoy</item>
        <item>Breach</item>
        <item>Omen</item>
        <item>Jett</item>
        <item>Raze</item>
        <item>Skye</item>
        <item>Yoru</item>
        <item>Astra</item>
        <item>Kay/o</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="matches">
        <item>Match Type</item>
        <item>Unrated</item>
        <item>Competitive</item>
        <item>Spike Rush</item>
        <item>Deathmatch</item>
        <item>Escalation</item>
        <item>Replication</item>
        <item>Snowball Fight</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="match_results">
        <item>Match Result</item>
        <item>WIN</item>
        <item>LOSE</item>
        <item>DRAW</item>
    </string-array>




    <!-- contentDescriptions -->
    <string name="icon_desc">Valorant Icon</string>

    <string name="match_see"><u>See Details</u></string>

    <!-- Agent Descriptions -->
    <string name="astra_desc">Ghanaian Agent Astra harnesses the energies of the cosmos to reshape battlefields to her whim. With full command of her astral form and a talent for deep strategic foresight, she\'\s always eons ahead of her enemy\'\s next move.</string>
    <string name="astra_ability1">ACTIVATE a Star to form a Gravity Well. Players in the area are pulled toward the center before it explodes, making all players still trapped inside vulnerable.</string>
    <string name="astra_ability2">ACTIVATE a Star to detonate a Nova Pulse. The Nova Pulse charges briefly then strikes, concussing all players in its area.</string>
    <string name="astra_ability3">ACTIVATE a Star to transform it into a Nebula (smoke). USE a Star to Dissipate it, returning the Star to be placed in a new location after a delay. Dissipate briefly forms a fake Nebula at the Star’s location before returning.</string>
    <string name="astra_ability4">ACTIVATE to enter Astral Form where you can place Stars with PRIMARY FIRE. Stars can be reactivated later, transforming them into a Nova Pulse, Nebula, or Gravity Well.</string>
    <string name="astra_ult">When Cosmic Divide is charged, use SECONDARY FIRE in Astral Form to begin aiming it, then PRIMARY FIRE to select two locations. An infinite Cosmic Divide connects the two points you select. Cosmic Divide blocks bullets and heavily dampens audio.</string>
    <string name="astra_tip1">Use Astra’s smokes. You can pick them up to fake smoke and spam after it dissipates.</string>
    <string name="astra_tip2">Enemies cannot hear you tap spike when you are behind the wall, so you can stick the defuse if you start it behind the wall</string>
    <string name="astra_tip3">You can combo your Astra pull with your teammates\'\ skills like Sova\'\s dart, Raze\'\s grenade and Killjoy\'\s molly.</string>

    <string name="breach_desc">Breach, the bionic Swede, fires powerful, targeted kinetic blasts to aggressively clear a path through enemy ground. The damage and disruption he inflicts ensures no fight is ever fair.</string>
    <string name="breach_ability1">EQUIP a fusion charge. FIRE the charge to set a slow-acting burst through the wall. The burst does heavy damage to anyone caught in its area.</string>
    <string name="breach_ability2">EQUIP a blinding charge. FIRE the charge to set a fast-acting burst through the wall. The charge detonates to blind all players looking at it.</string>
    <string name="breach_ability3">EQUIP a seismic blast. HOLD FIRE to increase the distance. RELEASE to set off the quake, dazing all players in its zone and in a line up to the zone.</string>
    <string name="breach_ult">EQUIP a seismic charge. FIRE to send a cascading quake through all terrain in a large line. The quake dazes and knocks up anyone caught in it.</string>
    <string name="breach_tip1">You can use your aftershock to make enemies push out of a corner.</string>
    <string name="breach_tip2">If you have a Jett on your team you can combo your flash with her dash in to make it safer for her to enter site</string>
    <string name="breach_tip3">Breach’s Ultimate can cancel a defuse so if you are low just hide somewhere near the spike and use your ultimate when you hear someone on the spike.</string>

    <string name="brim_desc">Joining from the USA, Brimstone\'\s orbital arsenal ensures his squad always has the advantage. His ability to deliver utility precisely and from a distance make him an unmatched boots-on-the-ground commander.</string>
    <string name="brim_ability1">INSTANTLY toss a stim beacon in front of Brimstone. Upon landing, the stim beacon will create a field that grants players RapidFire.</string>
    <string name="brim_ability2">EQUIP an incendiary grenade launcher. FIRE to launch a grenade that detonates as it comes to a rest on the floor, creating a lingering fire zone that damages players within the zone.</string>
    <string name="brim_ability3">EQUIP a tactical map. FIRE to set locations where Brimstone\'\s smoke clouds will land. ALTERNATE FIRE to confirm, launching long-lasting smoke clouds that block vision in the selected area.</string>
    <string name="brim_ult">EQUIP a tactical map. FIRE to launch a lingering orbital strike laser at the selected location, dealing high damage-over-time to players caught in the selected area.</string>
    <string name="brim_tip1">Always smoke where visuals are better for your teammates.</string>
    <string name="brim_tip2">Use a stim beacon whenever you can during fights, so you and your teammates have an upper hand.</string>
    <string name="brim_tip3">Learn simple lineups for post plants to ensure some rounds for your team.</string>

    <string name="cypher_desc">The Moroccan information broker, Cypher is a one-man surveillance network who keeps tabs on the enemy’s every move. No secret is safe. No maneuver goes unseen. Cypher is always watching.</string>
    <string name="cypher_ability1">EQUIP a trapwire. FIRE to place a destructible and covert tripwire at the targeted location, creating a line that spans between the placed location and the wall opposite. Enemy players who cross a tripwire will be tethered, revealed, and dazed after a short period if they do not destroy the device in time. This ability can be picked up to be REDEPLOYED.</string>
    <string name="cypher_ability2">INSTANTLY toss the cyber cage in front of Cypher. ACTIVATE to create a zone that blocks vision and plays an audio cue when enemies pass through it.</string>
    <string name="cypher_ability3">EQUIP a spycam. FIRE to place the spycam at the targeted location. RE-USE this ability to take control of the camera\'\s view. While in control of the camera, FIRE to shoot a marking dart. This dart will reveal the location of any player struck by the dart.</string>
    <string name="cypher_ult">INSTANTLY use on a dead enemy player in your crosshairs to reveal the location of all living enemy players.</string>
    <string name="cypher_tip1">Always keep your trip wires at waist level so enemies who want to flank cannot jump or crouch under them</string>
    <string name="cypher_tip2">Make sure utilize your smokes properly on both attacking and defending. When attacking use it to cover your opponents line of fire. While on defending use it to delay the push of enemies</string>
    <string name="cypher_tip3">Your camera is an essential skill for BOTH offense and defense. Always use it to watch for flanks on attacking. On defending make sure to position it on places where enemies cannot destroy it easily</string>

    <string name="jett_desc">Representing her home country of South Korea, Jett\'\s agile and evasive fighting style lets her take risks no one else can. She runs circles around every skirmish, cutting enemies before they even know what hit them.</string>
    <string name="jett_ability1">Holding the jump button while falling allows you to glide through the air.</string>
    <string name="jett_ability2">INSTANTLY throw a projectile that expands into a brief vision-blocking cloud on impact with a surface. HOLD the ability key to curve the smoke in the direction of your crosshair.</string>
    <string name="jett_ability3">INSTANTLY propel Jett high into the air.</string>
    <string name="jett_ability4">INSTANTLY propel Jett in the direction she is moving. If Jett is standing still, she will propel forward.</string>
    <string name="jett_ult">EQUIP a set of highly accurate throwing knives that recharge on killing an opponent. FIRE to throw a single knife at your target. ALTERNATE FIRE to throw all remaining daggers at your target.</string>
    <string name="jett_tip1">When using Jett’s ultimate, your shots are 100 percent accurate, so no matter how much you move, jump, and turn you will be accurate. Shoot your shot.</string>
    <string name="jett_tip2">When entering a site as Jett, you can smoke then dash in so enemies will not know where you land.</string>
    <string name="jett_tip3">When you can always revive your teammates. :)</string>

    <string name="kayo_desc">KAY/O is a machine of war built for a single purpose: neutralizing radiants. His power to suppress enemy abilities cripples his opponents\'\ capacity to fight back, securing him and his allies the ultimate edge.</string>
    <string name="kayo_ability1">EQUIP an explosive fragment. FIRE to throw. The fragment sticks to the floor and explodes multiple times, dealing near lethal damage at the center with each explosion.</string>
    <string name="kayo_ability2">EQUIP a flash grenade. FIRE to throw. The flash grenade explodes after a short fuse, blinding anyone in line of sight.</string>
    <string name="kayo_ability3">EQUIP a suppression blade. FIRE to throw. The blade sticks to the first surface it hits, winds up, and suppresses anyone in the radius of the explosion.</string>
    <string name="kayo_ult">INSTANTLY overload with polarized radianite energy that pulses from KAY/O in a massive radius. Enemies hit with pulses are suppressed for a short duration. While overloaded, KAY/O gains combat stim and can be re-stabilized if downed.</string>
    <string name="kayo_tip1">When playing Kay/o, you can right click his flash in corners to create a pop flash for the opponents to be blinded instantly.</string>
    <string name="kayo_tip2">When using Kay/o\'\s ultimate never be scared to push in because taking space with it is very important.</string>
    <string name="kayo_tip3">Kay/o’s knife can be used like sova arrows to detect if someone is on site. So if you know your line ups for Sova you can also use that for Kay/o.</string>

    <string name="killjoy_desc">The genius of Germany. Killjoy secures the battlefield with ease using her arsenal of inventions. If the damage from her gear doesn\'\t stop her enemies, her robots\'\ debuff will help make short work of them.</string>
    <string name="killjoy_ability1">EQUIP a Nanoswarm grenade. FIRE to throw the grenade. Upon landing, the Nanoswarm goes covert. ACTIVATE the Nanoswarm to deploy a damaging swarm of nanobots.</string>
    <string name="killjoy_ability2">EQUIP a covert Alarmbot. FIRE to deploy a bot that hunts down enemies that get in range. After reaching its target, the bot explodes and applies Vulnerable to enemies in the area. HOLD EQUIP to recall a deployed bot.</string>
    <string name="killjoy_ability3">EQUIP a Turret. FIRE to deploy a turret that automatically fires at enemies in a 180 degree cone. HOLD EQUIP to recall the deployed turret.</string>
    <string name="killjoy_ult">EQUIP the Lockdown device. FIRE to deploy the device. After a long windup, the device Detains all enemies caught in the radius. The device can be destroyed by enemies.</string>
    <string name="killjoy_tip1">Alarm Bots have a range so make sure to set them up properly so that it reaches you, so you won’t be flanked.</string>
    <string name="killjoy_tip2">Killjoy turrets are very annoying on pistol rounds. Place them in areas where the enemy cannot easily destroy them.</string>
    <string name="killjoy_tip3">Your Ultimate can either secure a push or delay a push so always know the right time to use it.</string>

    <string name="omen_desc">A phantom of a memory, Omen hunts in the shadows. He renders enemies blind, teleports across the field, then lets paranoia take hold as his foe scrambles to learn where he might strike next.</string>
    <string name="omen_ability1">EQUIP a shrouded step ability and see its range indicator. FIRE to begin a brief channel, then teleport to the marked location.</string>
    <string name="omen_ability2">EQUIP a blinding orb. FIRE to throw it forward, briefly reducing the vision range and deafening all players it touches. This projectile can pass through walls.</string>
    <string name="omen_ability3">EQUIP a shadow orb, entering a phased world to place and target the orbs. PRESS the ability key to throw the shadow orb to the marked location, creating a long-lasting shadow sphere that blocks vision. HOLD FIRE while targeting to move the marker further away. HOLD SECONDARY FIRE while targeting to move the marker closer. PRESS RELOAD to toggle normal targeting view.</string>
    <string name="omen_ult">EQUIP a tactical map. FIRE to begin teleporting to the selected location. While teleporting, Omen will appear as a Shade that can be destroyed by an enemy to cancel his teleport, or press EQUIP for Omen to cancel his teleport.</string>
    <string name="omen_tip1">Omen has one of the biggest flashes in-game meaning it could cover a whole corridor in one go. This is very useful when pushing choke points.</string>
    <string name="omen_tip2">Omen’s smokes can take to drop so while it is flying mid air you can try to teleport in to catch your opponents of guard.</string>
    <string name="omen_tip3">Your ultimate is a great flanking skill, so make sure to ult in places where opponents cannot hear you. Don’t be like the guy you just watched.</string>

    <string name="phoenix_desc">Hailing from the U.K., Phoenix\'\s star power shines through in his fighting style, igniting the battlefield with flash and flare. Whether he\'\s got backup or not, he\'\ll rush into a fight on his own terms.</string>
    <string name="phoenix_ability1">EQUIP a flame wall. FIRE to create a line of flames that moves forward, creating a wall that blocks vision and damages players passing through it. HOLD FIRE to bend the wall in the direction of your crosshair.</string>
    <string name="phoenix_ability2">EQUIP a flare orb that takes a curving path and detonates shortly after throwing. FIRE to curve the flare orb to the left, detonating and blinding any player who sees the orb. ALTERNATE FIRE to curve the flare orb to the right.</string>
    <string name="phoenix_ability3">EQUIP a fireball. FIRE to throw a fireball that explodes after a set amount of time or upon hitting the ground, creating a lingering fire zone that damages enemies.</string>
    <string name="phoenix_ult">INSTANTLY place a marker at Phoenix\'\s location. While this ability is active, dying or allowing the timer to expire will end this ability and bring Phoenix back to this location with full health.</string>
    <string name="phoenix_tip1">Always call your flash so you do not blind your teammates.</string>
    <string name="phoenix_tip2">When using your ultimate, stay in a safe spot so enemies will not camp your ultimate after you get reset.</string>
    <string name="phoenix_tip3">You can use your wall and molly to heal yourself if you are low.</string>

    <string name="raze_desc">Raze explodes out of Brazil with her big personality and big guns. With her blunt-force-trauma playstyle, she excels at flushing entrenched enemies and clearing tight spaces with a generous dose of \"boom.\"</string>
    <string name="raze_ability1">EQUIP a Boom Bot. FIRE will deploy the bot, causing it to travel in a straight line on the ground, bouncing off walls. The Boom Bot will lock on to any enemies in its frontal cone and chase them, exploding for heavy damage if it reaches them.</string>
    <string name="raze_ability2">INSTANTLY throw a Blast Pack that will stick to surfaces. RE-USE the ability after deployment to detonate, damaging and moving anything hit.</string>
    <string name="raze_ability3">EQUIP a cluster grenade. FIRE to throw the grenade, which does damage and creates sub-munitions, each doing damage to anyone in their range.</string>
    <string name="raze_ult">EQUIP a rocket launcher. FIRE shoots a rocket that does massive area damage on contact with anything.</string>
    <string name="raze_tip1">Raze satchels are very deadly when used correctly. But you can also use it to fly up to off angles where enemies do not usually check</string>
    <string name="raze_tip2">Line ups for Boom bots can also be found on youtube. If you are into that we suggest you guys watch Flights.</string>
    <string name="raze_tip3">When you want to ensure a round, use your ultimate when enemies tap the spike.</string>

    <string name="reyna_desc">Forged in the heart of Mexico, Reyna dominates single combat, popping off with each kill she scores. Her capability is only limited by her raw skill, making her highly dependent on performance.</string>
    <string name="reyna_ability1">EQUIP an ethereal, destructible eye. ACTIVATE to cast the eye a short distance forward. The eye will Nearsight all enemies who look at it.</string>
    <string name="reyna_ability2">INSTANTLY consume a nearby Soul Orb, rapidly healing for a short duration. Health gained through this skill exceeding 100 will decay over time. If Empress is active, this skill will automatically cast and not consume the Soul Orb.</string>
    <string name="reyna_ability3">INSTANTLY consume a nearby Soul Orb, becoming intangible for a short duration. If Empress is active, also become invisible.</string>
    <string name="reyna_ult">INSTANTLY enter a frenzy, increasing firing, equip and reload speed dramatically. Grants infinite charges of Soul Harvest abilities. When an enemy dies to Reyna, or dies within 3 seconds of taking damage from Reyna, the duration is renewed.</string>
    <string name="reyna_tip1">Blind going up or down so enemies won’t shoot it at head level to lessen the risk of getting shot in the head while your opponent is fully blinded.</string>
    <string name="reyna_tip2">After getting a kill, you can use your dismiss to peek around corners and get information safely for your team.</string>
    <string name="reyna_tip3">Never go for the heal, always make sure to be safe when sucking your opponent’s dry.</string>

    <string name="sage_desc">The stronghold of China, Sage creates safety for herself and her team wherever she goes. Able to revive fallen friends and stave off aggressive pushes, she provides a calm center to a hellish fight.</string>
    <string name="sage_ability1">EQUIP a barrier orb. FIRE places a wall that fortifies after a few seconds. ALT FIRE rotates the targeter.</string>
    <string name="sage_ability2">EQUIP a slowing orb. FIRE to throw a slowing orb forward that detonates upon landing, creating a lingering field that slows players caught inside of it.</string>
    <string name="sage_ability3">EQUIP a healing orb. FIRE with your crosshairs over a damaged ally to activate a heal-over-time on them. ALT FIRE while Sage is damaged to activate a self heal-over-time.</string>
    <string name="sage_ult">EQUIP a resurrection ability. FIRE with your crosshairs placed over a dead ally to begin resurrecting them. After a brief channel, the ally will be brought back to life with full health.</string>
    <string name="sage_tip1">You can bait opponents with your resurrection then swing off it after to catch your opponents off guard.</string>
    <string name="sage_tip2">When you have Skye on your team make sure to heal her because you can make her heal your allies instead.</string>
    <string name="sage_tip3">Walls are not only used to block an entrance. You can also use it to get a cheeky off angle on your opponents.</string>

    <string name="skye_desc">Hailing from Australia, Skye and her band of beasts trail-blaze the way through hostile territory. With her creations hampering the enemy, and her power to heal others, the team is strongest and safest by Skye’s side.</string>
    <string name="skye_ability1">EQUIP a healing trinket. HOLD FIRE to channel, healing allies in range and line of sight. Can be reused until her healing pool is depleted. Skye cannot heal herself.</string>
    <string name="skye_ability2">EQUIP a Tasmanian tiger trinket. FIRE to send out and take control of the predator. While in control, FIRE to leap forward, exploding in a concussive blast and damaging directly hit enemies.</string>
    <string name="skye_ability3">EQUIP a hawk trinket. FIRE to send it forward. HOLD FIRE to guide the hawk in the direction of your crosshair. RE-USE while the hawk is in flight to transform it into a flash that plays a hit confirm if an enemy was within range and line of sight.</string>
    <string name="skye_ult">EQUIP a Seeker trinket. FIRE to send out three Seekers to track down the three closest enemies. If a Seeker reaches its target, it nearsights them.</string>
    <string name="skye_tip1">Using Skye’s blinds, you can gather information by listening to the sound queues when Skye says blinded.</string>
    <string name="skye_tip2">Use your ultimate when 3 opponents are alive to get all of their locations.</string>
    <string name="skye_tip3">Skye’s dog can help you clear angles safer so always use it before entering.</string>

    <string name="sova_desc">Born from the eternal winter of Russia\'\s tundra, Sova tracks, finds, and eliminates enemies with ruthless efficiency and precision. His custom bow and incredible scouting abilities ensure that even if you run, you cannot hide.</string>
    <string name="sova_ability1">EQUIP an owl drone. FIRE to deploy and take control of movement of the drone. While in control of the drone, FIRE to shoot a marking dart. This dart will reveal the location of any player struck by the dart.</string>
    <string name="sova_ability2">EQUIP a bow with shock bolt. FIRE to send the explosive bolt forward, detonating upon collision and damaging players nearby. HOLD FIRE to extend the range of the projectile. ALTERNATE FIRE to add up to two bounces to this arrow.</string>
    <string name="sova_ability3">EQUIP a bow with recon bolt. FIRE to send the recon bolt forward, activating upon collision and revealing the location of nearby enemies caught in the line of sight of the bolt. Enemies can destroy this bolt. HOLD FIRE to extend the range of the projectile. ALTERNATE FIRE to add up to two bounces to this arrow.</string>
    <string name="sova_ult">EQUIP a bow with three long-range, wall-piercing energy blasts. FIRE to release an energy blast in a line in front of Sova, dealing damage and revealing the location of enemies caught in the line. This ability can be RE-USED up to two more times while the ability timer is active.</string>
    <string name="sova_tip1">Sova is primarily for providing valuable intel to your team throughout the round. Learn to hang back.</string>
    <string name="sova_tip2">Hunting for picks and revealing opponent positions is tempting but use your abilities from behind cover or a safe distance.</string>
    <string name="sova_tip3">You can use your ultimate to get easy kills on your opponents.</string>

    <string name="viper_desc">EQUIP a chemical launcher. FIRE to launch a canister that shatters upon hitting the floor, creating a lingering chemical zone that damages and applies Vulnerable.</string>
    <string name="viper_ability1">EQUIP a chemical launcher. FIRE to launch a canister that shatters upon hitting the floor, creating a lingering chemical zone that damages and applies Vulnerable.</string>
    <string name="viper_ability2">EQUIP a gas emitter. FIRE to throw the emitter that perpetually remains throughout the round. RE-USE the ability to create a toxic gas cloud at the cost of fuel. This ability can be RE-USED more than once and can be picked up to be REDEPLOYED.</string>
    <string name="viper_ability3">EQUIP a gas emitter launcher. FIRE to deploy a long line of gas emitters. RE-USE the ability to create a tall wall of toxic gas at the cost of fuel. This ability can be RE-USED more than once.</string>
    <string name="viper_ult">EQUIP a chemical sprayer. FIRE to spray a chemical cloud in all directions around Viper, creating a large cloud that reduces the vision range of players and maximum health of enemies inside of it. HOLD the ability key to disperse the cloud early.</string>
    <string name="viper_tip1">There are easy one way smokes in different maps so it would be good to learn some from Viper set ups.</string>
    <string name="viper_tip2">Your wall can also be used post-plant to retake the spike from the opponents.</string>
    <string name="viper_tip3">Look up or down in Vipers ultimate to see farther in your smoke.</string>

    <string name="yoru_desc">Japanese native, Yoru, rips holes straight through reality to infiltrate enemy lines unseen. Using deception and aggression in equal measure, he gets the drop on each target before they know where to look.</string>
    <string name="yoru_ability1">EQUIP an echo that mimics footsteps when activated. FIRE to activate and send the echo forward. ALT FIRE to place an echo in place. USE the inactive echo to send it forward.</string>
    <string name="yoru_ability2">EQUIP to rip an unstable dimensional fragment from reality. FIRE to throw the fragment, activating a flash that winds up once it collides with a hard surface in world.</string>
    <string name="yoru_ability3">EQUIP to harness a rift tether. FIRE to send the tether out moving forward. ALT FIRE to place a tether in place. ACTIVATE to teleport to the tether\'\s location.</string>
    <string name="yoru_ult">EQUIP a mask that can see between dimensions. FIRE to drift into Yoru\'\s dimension, unable to be affected or seen by enemies from the outside.</string>
    <string name="yoru_tip1">You can throw Yoru’s flash from a far distance so you can help your teammates get out of a sticky situation</string>
    <string name="yoru_tip2">You can bait out Killjoys skill with your footsteps to trigger the bots.</string>
    <string name="yoru_tip3">In your Ultimate you can use a shorty or spectre to get easy kills because it has the fastest pull-out time.</string>
</resources>